<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neubloc - www.neubloc.pl</title>
    <description>Neubloc Polska Sp. z o.o.</description>
    <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io</link>
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Why RightSource to South America?</title>
          <description>								&lt;p&gt;South America might not seem like a possibility when outsourcing software development, but with Argentina and Ecuador emerging as the next IT hotspots, Neubloc encourages companies to rethink their outsourcing destination. Neubloc also offers its development and “follow the sun” models to help companies RightSource the “right” way.

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-27T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/37-why-rightsource-to-south-america/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/37-why-rightsource-to-south-america/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Jest w Polsce nowym Hotspot IT?</title>
          <description>								&lt;p&gt;India has long dominated other countries as the top destination for outsourcing Information Technology (IT), but with the rise in attrition rates and other fall outs, is there a better alternative? Some companies seem to think so and they are looking to Poland.

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-20T01:29:33+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/36-poland-the-new-it-hotspot/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/36-poland-the-new-it-hotspot/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Costs of Outsourcing to Poland</title>
          <description>    &lt;p&gt;Only a decade or so ago, well-educated Poles and fresh graduates had to venture outside Poland to find jobs in the IT and software development sectors. Now, outsourcing for IT and software development is Poland’s largest employment sector. Even software giants outside the US and Western Europe, like Infosys from India, are shifting projects to Poland.

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-20T01:29:33+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/34-costs-of-outsourcing-to-poland/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/34-costs-of-outsourcing-to-poland/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>How and Where to Outsource your Development</title>
          <description>								&lt;p&gt;For a startup, outsourcing product development is not easy. In contrast, large companies routinely establish outsource development operations because they have greater time, scale, resources and brand recognition to attract and maintain engineering talent. Even without size or leverage, outsourced product development is the only realistic option for early stage technology companies. So how do you ensure proper partner selection and good management to outsource successfully? Read on!

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-20T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/35-how-and-where-to-outsource-your-development/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/35-how-and-where-to-outsource-your-development/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Costs of Outsourcing to China and India</title>
          <description>    &lt;p&gt;For companies in the United States and Western Europe looking to outsource, India and China are no longer the only choices. Outsourcing has bolstered India’s booming IT industry and China’s unparalleled manufacturing sector throughout the years, raising the standard of living. These changes have had long term effects and have significantly changed the costs of outsourcing to these countries.

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-20T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/33-costs-of-outsourcing-china-and-india/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/33-costs-of-outsourcing-china-and-india/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Advantages of Using Co-Design 2</title>
          <description>In today’s global and fast-paced economy, outsourcing provides enriching opportunities for companies that save both time and money. However, in order to make the most of these third parties, it is important to understand their advantages as well as their disadvantages.</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-18T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/10-testpost/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/10-testpost/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Conducting Co-Design Sessions</title>
          <description>    &lt;p&gt;Because the co-design approach is iterative, it is necessary for all design engineers, developers, and target users to assemble for mapping future steps. Conducting these sessions is all about careful planning. First, confirm all attendees and ensure they are notified of the dates and times.

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/32-conducting-co-design-sessions/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/32-conducting-co-design-sessions/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Pros and Cons of Outsourcing Software Design and Development</title>
          <description>In today’s global and fast-paced economy, outsourcing provides enriching opportunities for companies that save both time and money. However, in order to make the most of these third parties, it is important to understand their advantages as well as their disadvantages.</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/31-pros-and-cons-of-outsourcing/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/31-pros-and-cons-of-outsourcing/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Product Planning and Co-Design: How to Solve the Problem</title>
          <description>    &lt;p&gt;Good product design effectively and efficiently meets the user’s function and because of this, defining the user is a crucial step that must be completed before beginning design. To accomplish this, user profiles are created that target market segmentation and address the user’s:

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/30-co-design-how-to-solve-the-problem/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/30-co-design-how-to-solve-the-problem/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Market Research: Discovering the “What”</title>
          <description>								&lt;p&gt;The first step to effective market research is to gather field data from users in their daily context. Techniques used to understand user goals and tasks include:

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/27-market-research-discovering-the-what/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/27-market-research-discovering-the-what/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Problems with Outsourcing to India</title>
          <description>&lt;h4&gt;by Armando Viteri, Neubloc, CEO and President&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With major backlash against outsourcing to India, many companies with investments there are now looking for alternatives. Although there is discussion on the wage structure, the issues of outsourcing development services in India are deeper. This paper explores the continual issues with outsourcing development services to India and the shift to other alternatives. 

</description>
          <pubDate>2014-02-17T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/20-problems-with-outsourcing-to-india/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/20-problems-with-outsourcing-to-india/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Advantages of Using Co-Design</title>
          <description>In today’s global and fast-paced economy, outsourcing provides enriching opportunities for companies that save both time and money. However, in order to make the most of these third parties, it is important to understand their advantages as well as their disadvantages.</description>
          <pubDate>2014-01-07T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
          <link>http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/advantages-of-using-co-design/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://neubloc-poland.github.io/blog/advantages-of-using-co-design/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>